♪ It seems today that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely?♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy♪
♪ Lucky there's a man who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us♪
♪ Laugh and cry♪
♪ He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
电话女郎
Call Girl
亦有"应召女郎"之意
翻译&注释:wudixny 校对&压制:Zurica @familyguy贴吧字幕组
嘿 Chris 你拿的是什么
Hey, Chris, what do you got there?
我今天在学校建了栋鸟舍
I made a birdhouse at school today.
噢 看着超像"管家本森"里的州长官邸
Oh, looks an awful lot like the Governor's Mansion from Benson.
ABC台 1979-1986年 播出的情景喜剧
是的 我喜欢那部剧
It is. I'm fond of the series,
所以我想让当地的鸟儿们也知道
and I wanted the local birds to be aware of that.
那么 我会留意着那些极好的山雀们(咪咪)
Well, I'll be on the lookout for great tits.
Peter!
Lois 那其实是一种鸟
Well, actually, Lois, that's a species of bird
众所周知是国内鸟舍中最常见的一种
that's known to frequent domestic birdhouses.
这就是为啥我总想要个鸟舍
It's why I've always wanted a birdhouse.
嘿 Lois  我们一起出去
Hey, Lois, let's go outside
看知否能找到点极好的山雀(咪咪)吧
and see if we can find some great tits.
因为这房子里肯定是没有的
'Cause there certainly ain't any in here!
还记得我们昨晚看到的那两只么
Remember those two we saw last night?
其中一只比另一只大
One was bigger than the other.
没错 而且较大那只的尖端还有根毛伸出来
Yeah, and-and the bigger one had a hair sticking out of that pointy thing.
那玩意儿叫什么来着?
What do you call that pointy thing, again?
- 喙 - 好吧
- The beak? - Okay.
来吧 老爸
Come on, Dad!
也许我们能让鸟儿们演出"管家本森"里的剧情
Maybe we can get the birds to act out the Benson
在那集中混乱的日程安排让州长纠结于
where a scheduling snafu forces the governor to decide
是去会见总统还是看女儿Katie的校园剧
between meeting the president or going to Katie's school play!
吔
Yay!
糊涂州长
Scatterbrained governor.
安置好了
Welp, there she is.
一栋鸟舍
A birdhouse.
我只希望搬进来的鸟儿不要介意隔壁的波斯鸟
I just hope whoever moves in doesn't mind the Persian birds next door.
呃 吱吱 吱吱
Eh, tweet, tweet.
瞧瞧咱奢侈的喷泉
Check out my expensive fountain.
老爸 瞧
Dad, look.
你建了栋了不起的鸟舍 儿子
You built a great birdhouse, son.
我真为你骄傲
I'm real proud of you.
谢了 爸
Thanks, Dad.
不
No!
刚才发生了什么
What just happened?!
那是什么东西
What was that thing?!
我不知道 某种超级鸟
I don't know. Some kind of super bird.
或者是一只买了博飞健身器材的普通鸟
Or maybe an average bird who bought a Bowflex.
那只超级鸟毁了一切
Well, that super bird ruined everything!
没错 一个不可忽视的力量
Indeed, a force to be reckoned with,
就像能源部部长朱棣文
like Secretary of Energy Steven Chu.
朱部长 筹款委员会已经送来了初步预算
Secretary Chu, Ways and Means has sent over a preliminary budget.
看来能源部要减少4%的预算了
It looks like the Department of Energy is looking at a four-percent budget cut.
好不 不削减预算
Okay, no budget cut.
不许削减预算
No budget cut.
看见你们父亲了没
Has anyone seen your father?
都快6点了
It's almost 6:00.
我在这儿呢
PETER: I am here.
家人们 来见见我的猎鹰 Xerxes
Family, I want you to meet my falcon, Xerxes.
我现在是训鹰者了
I'm a falconer now.
可我的圣诞节礼物依旧是打包的炒蛋
And yet for Christmas, I got a wrapped scrambled egg.
Peter 那鹰看上去很危险
Peter, that falcon looks pretty dangerous.
是啊 Peter 赶紧把它弄走 吃晚饭吧
Yeah, Peter, get rid of that thing right now and eat your dinner.
不要
No!
我是个训鹰者
I am a falconer
我会吃Xerxes带给我的任何东西
and I will eat whatever Xerxes brings me.
给主人找吃的
Feed master.
Peter 搞毛啊
Peter, what the hell?
对Xerxes 每顿饭都是盛宴
For Xerxes, every meal is a pageant.
嘿 Peter
Hey, Peter.
噢 猎鹰 酷
Oh, falcon. Cool.
嗨 猎鹰
Hi, falcon.
喔 喔 放松 伙计
Whoa, whoa, easy there, fella.
Xerxes 他叫Xerxes
Xerxes. His name is Xerxes.
呃 他吃什么
Uh, what does Xerxes eat?
啮齿动物 现在如果你不介意的话...
Rodents. Now if you'll excuse me...
搞什么鬼
What the hell?!
Peter 让他住手
Peter, make him stop!
嘿 你那下面是有什么东西啊 quagmire
Hey, what do you got going on down there, Quagmire?
你藏了 你藏了只老鼠么
You got a, you got a rodent situation?
哦 没有
Uh, no!
但看来Xerxes认为那儿有
Well, Xerxes seems to think there is.
把他弄下去 Peter
Get him off, Peter!
承认你有只老鼠在里面吧
Admit you got a rodent in there.
- Peter - 承认
- Peter! - Admit it!
靠 你吓的他从前面跑了
Aw, you scared him out the front.
Tony 回来
Tony, come back!
噢 怎...怎么...
Oh, what... what...
我该怎么办 我该怎么办
What do I do? What do I do?
只能希望他没站在你的囟门上
Well, just hope he's not standing on your soft spot.
有那个可能么
Well, is that possible?
那样可就把我给废...
Because that could really mess up my...
妈 给我午饭钱
Mom, I need money for lunch.
天啊
Oh, God.
抱歉 Chris
I'm sorry, Chris.
我的钱包已经丢了一天了
My purse has been missing for a day now.
我-我到处都找不到
I-I can't find it anywhere.
别担心 Lois
Not to worry, Lois.
Xerxes会找到它的
Xerxes will find it.
Xerxes去找Lois的钱包
Xerxes, find Lois's purse.
现在这是你的钱包了
This is your purse now.
Peter 我可不能把钱装这里面
Peter, I can't carry my money in this.
没错 "她的"钱
Yeah, her money.
你会爱上那公园的 Xerxes
You're gonna love the park, Xerxes.
我想你知道我想要什么
I think you know what I want.
太酷了
This is awesome.
我们应该有自己的电视剧
We should have our own TV show.
Peter与边斗猎鹰
那你觉得柏拉图式的淋浴怎么样
So what do you think about a platonic shower?
你是Peter Griffin么
Are you Peter Griffin?
我是
Yes, sir, I am.
我是你昨天盗窃的摩托车失主的代理人
I represent the man whose sidecar motorcycle you stole yesterday.
你激起了我的兴趣 继续说
You've piqued my interest, go on.
对你来说不幸的是 这人非常非常犹太
Unfortunately for you, that man is very, very Jewish
准备诉求你的一切财产
and is suing you for everything you've got.
包括这只隼
Including the falcon.
不 不要拿走Xerxes
No! Not Xerxes!
你逃不掉的
You won't get away with this.
等美航杂志知道这事你就完了
Wait till American Airlines' magazine hears about this!
你好 是美航杂志么
Hello, American Airlines' magazine?
我有个大料要爆给你们
Have I got a scoop for you.
"猎鹰被偷"
"Falcon stolen."
恶 这里面还有个脚指甲
Ew, there's a toenail in this.
我想我还是继续咳嗽算了
Guess I'll just go back to coughing.
现在我们该怎么办
Now what are we gonna do?
我们没钱了
We have no money.
没事儿 Lois 我们有一个美满的家庭
That's okay, Lois, we got a wonderful family.
才不
No, we don't.
我们有Meg 笨蛋和大头
There's Meg and Dummy and Big Head.
妈的 Peter
Damn it, Peter,
我不得不去找份工作了
I'm probably gonna have to get a job.
谢天谢地 我还以为自己得回
Oh, thank God. Thought I was gonna have to go back
那个"Kelly和Peter直播秀"呢
to being on Live with Kelly and Peter.
恶搞美国的一档早间新闻节目"Live! with Kelly and Michael"
嘉宾介绍自己时要保持张嘴微笑真是累死我也
So exhausting having to do that open-mouth smile while the guest does their bit.
今天和我们一起的是"傲骨贤妻"中的克里斯汀·芭伦斯基
We're here with The Good Wife's Christine Baranski.
CBS的一部政律剧 由其本人配音
那么 克里斯汀 你真的赢过一座艾美奖
So, Christine, you've actually won an Emmy,
是这样么
is that right?
没错 因"西碧儿"中的Maryann一角
Yes, for playing Maryann on Cybill.
CBS台1995-1998年的情景喜剧 她于1995年获得艾美最佳女配角
啊
Ah.
但是我在"傲骨贤妻"中的角色
But my character on The Good Wife
却与Maryann截然不同
is such a complete departure from Maryann.
啊
Ah!
你的舞台经验也非常丰富
You've also had quite a stage career.
我想你赢过一次托尼奖对吧
I believe you won a Tony Award?
其实 我赢过两次
Well, actually, I've won two.
1984年的最佳女演员(The Real Thing) 和2008年的最佳改编戏剧(Boeing Boeing)
啊
Ah!
再问一句 达令
And one more question, darling.
你是谁来着
Who are you?
[职业介绍所]
抱歉 您能看下我的简历么
Excuse me, would you mind taking a look at my résumé?
我已经有段时间没面试过了
I haven't had an interview in a while,
我想确认下格式是否正确
and I want to make sure it's formatted correctly.
1992.9--至今: 家庭主妇
- 看着不错 - 好的
- Looks okay. - Good.
没有太夸张吧
It's not too braggy?
嗨 打扰了
Hi, I'm sorry,
由吉奥瓦尼·瑞比西配音 "老友记"中菲比的弟弟 "泰迪熊"中小胖子的变态爸爸
我忍不住偷听你说话
I couldn't help but overhear you.
你的声音真是美极了
You have an amazing speaking voice.
我叫Randy
My name's Randy.
我可以给声音如此优美的你一份稳定工作
I can get you steady work with a voice like that.
真的么
Really?
喔 谢谢你
Wow, thank you.
这太好了
This is great.
现在我不用成为玫琳凯的女推销员了
Now I won't have to become a Mary Kay saleswoman.
那么 这些香波
So, what makes these shampoos
和超市里的有什么不同呢
different from the ones at the supermarket?
这些香波曾在我车里待过
These shampoos have been in my car.
各位猜猜怎么着
Guess what everybody?
天啊 难道你买了卫生棉和杂货?
Oh, my God! Tampons and groceries?
不-- 不过也对-- 但我今天也被伯乐发现了
No-- well, yes-- but also I got discovered today.
我或许会为一个著名的旁白艺人
I could be one of those famous voice-over artists
你们会从电视或电影中听到我的声音
you hear on TV or in the movies.
呃 她说画外音?
Ugh, her doing voice-over?
谁会想听啊
Who wants to hear that?
也许她会成为那种烦人的声音之一
Maybe she could be one of those annoying voices
就像"不不不 不是那种商品"
that goes, "Ah, ah, ah, not that product."
这几种主要牌子的罐头汤中
NARRATOR: Which of these leading brands of canned soup
哪种含盐不超过100克的?
has less than a hundred grams of sodium?
"不不不 继续找"
Ah, ah, ah.Keep going.
"不是那个"
Not that one.
[丰盛的选择牌]
"不不不"
Ah, ah, ah.
"也不是那个"
Not that one either.
[美国碗牌]
"不不不"
Ah, ah, ah.
"不 不是那种"
Nope, not that one.
[新鲜厨房牌]
听着 这都不是给我买的
Look, this isn't even for me.
是给我的同性恋人
It's for my homosexual lover.
"不不不"
Ah, ah, ah.
"圣经关于那点说的很明白了"
The Bible's pretty clear about that.
嗨 我是Lois Griffin
Hi, I'm Lois Griffin.
我约了见Randy
I have an appointment to see Randy.
Lois 我很高兴你决定来试试
Lois, I'm so glad you decided to try this.
不敢相信我现在是名人了
I can't believe I'm a celebrity now.
我也可以在回家路上为了找乐子而撞个人了
I might hit someone with my car on the way home just for kicks.
我有预感你会成为这儿的大明星的
Well, I have a feeling you're gonna be a big star here.
我穿的什么?
What am I wearing?
一丝不挂 甜心
Nothing at all, sweetheart.
等会儿
Wait a minute.
这是个色情电话机构
This is a phone sex operation.
我不能这么做
I can't do this.
一周2千刀 宝贝儿
It pays two grand a week, sweetie.
天啊
Oh, my God.
有了这笔钱
With that type of money,
我都能买威廉姆斯-索纳玛牌的厨具了
I could buy pots and pans at Williams-Sonoma.
世界著名厨具品牌
这一套非常不错
This is a very nice set.
你一定是个电话妓女了
You must be a phone whore.
用菊花想都知道
You bet your sweet ass I am.
好了 Lois 你知道该怎么做
All right, Lois, you know the drill.
不管你做什么
And whatever you do,
不要提及电脑和网络
do not mention computers or the Internet.
不能让他们知道
They cannot know about it.
哦 天
Oh, dear.
喂?
Hello?
呃 你-你好...
Uh, h-hi there...
...猛男
...sexy.
我听得出你一定是老手了
I can tell you're good at this.
听着 我想和我儿子在电话上和你来个双飞
Listen, I want to double-team you on the phone with my son.
噢
Oh.
没错 我们家已经有点分崩离析了
Yeah, the family's kind of falling apart.
所以我只想 呃...
And I'm just, uh...
只是一个父亲想要努力维持家庭的和睦
just a dad trying to keep it all together.
我明白了
I see.
你喜欢坐轮椅的男人么
Are you into guys in wheelchairs?
并不
Not really.
哦 那就太糟了
Oh, that's too bad,
因为 呃 我儿子是坐轮椅的
'cause, uh, my son's in a wheelchair.
嘿 Lois
Hey, Lois.
那么 你第一天旁白的工作如何啊
So, how was your first day of voice-over?
呃 没什么啦
Eh, it was nothing.
原来 我只是给非常晦涩的欧洲广告做旁白
Turns out, I'm just doing very obscure European commercials.
其实 我也该让自己重出江湖了
You know, I have got to get myself back out there, too.
自从Stewman组合后我就没表演过了
I haven't performed since I was in Stewman Group.
恶搞Blue Man Group(蓝人乐队)
我不明白 这啥玩意儿
I don't get it. What is this?
我们也不知道
We don't know either.
嗨 我是...
Hi, my name's...
小雅
Classy.
我能为你做什么 猛男
What can I do for you, hot stuff?
噢 你好 小雅
Ooh, hi, Classy.
听着 你有皮夹或钱包么
Listen, do you have a wallet or a purse?
呃 我有个钱包
Uh, I have a purse.
噢
Oh.
噢 宝贝儿
Oh, baby.
我要你把钱拿出来然后非常慢的点钱
I want you to take the money out and count it really slowly.
好的
Okay.
一
One.
呜 很好
Ooh, that's nice.
二
Two.
噢 噢 天啊
Oh. Oh, my.
抱歉 我包里的下一张是十块的
I'm sorry, the next bill I have in here is a ten.
噢
Oh!
噢 我爱你
Oh, I love you!
爱所有的一切
All that and everything.
嗨 我是小雅
Hi, I'm Classy.
好啊 让我们开始吧 甜妞
All right, let's get this going, sweet cheeks.
你有手绢么
You got a handkerchief?
呃 有
Uh, yeah.
好的 团成团然后塞进你嘴里
Good, ball that up and stick it in your mouth.
好了
Okay.
现在 你还有什么东西
Now, what else you got there?
你有订书机么
You got a stapler?
嗯哼 有
Uh-huh, uh, yeah.
好 那你为何不继续
Okay, why don't you go ahead
把它也塞进你嘴里呢
and stick that in your mouth, too.
再塞个鼠标垫怎么样
How about a mouse pad?
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
耶 继续把它卷起来
Yeah, go ahead and roll that up
然后塞进去
and stuff it in there.
你有没有入职时HR给你的资料夹
Did you get a packet from HR when you started working there?
好 我就当你说是了
Okay, I'll take that as a yes.
我也很确定你知道我想让你怎么用它
And I'm pretty certain you know what I want you to do with it.
好了 你觉得你还能往嘴里塞东西么
Okay, you think you can fit anything else in your mouth?
- 不行 - 那好 现在我们开始往其他地方塞东西吧
- Mm-mm. - All right, so now let's start filling up some other places.
Peter 我今天工作了一整天
Peter, I've had a long day at work,
现在 我最不想的就是做爱了
and right now, sex is the last thing I want to think about.
搞毛啊 Lois
What the hell, Lois?
你永远都不会想再做了
You never want to do it no more.
如果我告诉你我憋了一大泡屎呢
What if I told you I'm holding in a very big dump?
Peter 你今晚就不能用袜子Lois解决么
Peter, can't you just use Sock Lois tonight?
不 袜子Lois对我来说已经不再真实了
No! Sock Lois doesn't feel authentic to me anymore.
嘿 Joe 你和Bonnie多久上次床?
Hey, Joe, how often do you have sex with Bonnie?
医保组织一年只替我付一次设备费用 为什么问这个
Well, my HMO only pays for the equipment once a year. Why?
Lois 现在几乎没有性趣了
Lois barely wants to do it no more.
我都快疯了
I'm going crazy here.
呃 我明白
Ugh. I hear you.
嘿 Quagmire 帮你自己一个忙:
Hey, Quagmire, do yourself a favor:
不要结婚
don't get married.
我就没这打算
I wasn't gonna.
好的 不要结
Good. Don't.
没这打算
I wasn't.
很好 不要结
Perfect. Don't.
Joe 你让我"不要结婚"的话对我完全没影响
Joe, you telling me not to has no effect on me whatsoever.
我就不打算结婚
I'm not gonna get married.
很好 不要结
Great. Don't.
说真的 各位 这个无性生活完全行不同
I mean it, you guys, this no-sex thing doesn't work.
我需要某种发泄
I need some kind of outlet.
知道么 Peter 我正好有你需要的东西
You know, Peter, I got just the thing for you.
我最近和一个新的色情电话妞通过话
There's this new phone sex chick I been calling,
她棒极了
and she is amazing.
天 我不知道 这算不算背叛Lois呢
Gee, I don't know. Isn't that cheating on Lois?
不 听着 这是在电话上的
No, look, it's over the phone.
有这么种说法:"电话不算打炮"
It's like they say: "Phonin' ain't bonin'."
好吧 那我想我该试试看
Yeah. Well, I guess I could try it.
相信我 Peter
Trust me, Peter.
嘿 我告诉你去看妇科专家没错吧 对不
Hey, I was right about telling you to go see the gynecologist, wasn't I?
请让我看些鲍鱼
I'd like to see some vaginas, please.
我们来这儿不就是为此么 进来吧
That's what we're here for. Come on in.
你好 帅哥
Hello there, handsome.
我是小雅
I'm Classy.
呃 嗨 小雅 我是 呃 Peter
Um, hi, Classy, I'm, uh, Peter.
Peter...
Night Shyamalan.
他们这样叫我是因为我那东西最后有一个大螺旋
They call me that 'cause I got a big twist at the end of my thing.
天啊
Oh, my God.
呃... 那个 你好 Peter
Um... well, hello, Peter.
我能为你做点什么
What can I do for you?
呃 你想看看我画的画么
Um, you want to see some pictures that I drew?
呃 好啊
Um, sure.
这是我骑在大象上
This is me on a elephant.
哇 画得很美
Wow. That's beautiful.
你是自己一个人画完的?
Did you draw that all by yourself?
没错
Uh-huh.
然后这张是我在月球上
And this is me on the moon.
我并没有真去那儿
I didn't really go there.
是在我的想象之中而已
It was just in my imagination,
所以我画了出来
so I drawed it.
哇 你真是有天赋呢
Wow, you're really talented.
知道么 你有一种东西 小雅
You know, there's something about you, Classy.
一种特殊的东西
Something special.
啊 你嘴真甜
Aw, that's very sweet.
我喜欢你的声音
I like your voice.
让我想听到更多你的声音
It makes me want to hear more of your voice.
嘿 你想看搞笑漫画么
Hey, you want to see a funny comic?
好啊
Sure.
苹果艾伦的疯狂冒险
"那是我"
[开心一笑]
某个早晨艾伦醒来发现
"我的朋友们都去哪儿了?"
"啊啊啊啊"
他吓坏了因为他的朋友都死在派里了
He's scared 'cause his friends got killed in the pie.
那么 Peter 你今天过得如何
So, Peter, how was your day?
呃 一般般吧
Eh, it was okay.
除了那个我当午饭的横滨牛肉饭
Except for that Yokohama beef bowl I tried for lunch.
没想象的好
Not sitting so well.
只是"一般"?
Just "okay"?
你今天没尝试什么新东西么
Didn't try anything new today?
没和什么有趣的人说话?
Talk to anyone interesting?
没有
No, not really.
噢 那碗牛肉饭把我吃坏了
Oh, that beef bowl is wrecking me.
我的胃感觉就像上次
My stomach feels like that time
我得了爆炸性腹泻一样
I had explosive diarrhea.
屎屋
Brown house.
"road house"经典段子
喂?
Hello?
呃 嗨 小雅
Um, hi, Classy.
是Peter
It's Peter.
噢 你好
Oh, hi there.
我喜欢你说话的样子
I love when you talk.
听着 呃 我这几次和你通话很开心
Listen, um, I've had such a good time talking to you these past few times
所以我想也许我们能见个面
that I was thinking maybe we could meet.
但是你结婚了啊
But you're married!
你有老婆
You've got a wife!
没错 但她最近对我总是很冷淡
Yeah, but she's been giving me the cold shoulder lately.
再说 就算发生了那种事
Besides, anything that comes out,
我总能回家后摆平她
I can always take home to her.
我觉得这不太好
I don't think this is a good idea.
我是说 欺骗你的妻子是很严重的
I mean, cheating on your wife is a very serious thing.
你不明白 我必须要见你
You don't understand, I have to meet you.
我-我知道有些唐突
I-I know it seems sudden,
但我感觉我们之间有种特殊的感觉
but I feel a special connection with you.
听着 告诉我地点时间
Look, you name the place and the time,
我会到的
and I'll be there.
你个贱货
You son of a bitch!
好的
Okay.
我会去见你的
I'll meet you.
吔 我成功了
Yay, I did it!
谢谢 仙女Peter
Thanks, Fairy God Peter!
Peter 力量一直与你同在
Peter, the power was within you all along.
现在如果你不介意 我要去和仙女Quagmire
Now if you'll excuse me, I'm meeting Fairy God Quagmire
还有仙女Joe在仙女醉蚌吧见面了
and Fairy God Joe down at the Fairy God Clam.
- 那听着像个基吧 - 那就是个基吧
- That sounds like a gay bar. - It is a gay bar.
没错 伙计们 我要见到她了
That's right, fellas, I'm gonna meet her.
见谁?
Meet who?
是啊 你在说什么呢
Yeah, what are you talking about?
哦 我以为我们从一半开始是节省时间呢
Oh, I-I thought we were starting in the middle to save time.
那个色情电话女郎
The-the phone sex lady,
我要见到那个色情电话女郎的真人了
I'm gonna meet the phone sex lady in person.
哇 哇 哇 等会儿 Peter
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait a minute, Peter.
是我就不会那么做
I wouldn't do that.
打住 Quagmire 你这主意可不好
Hang on, Quagmire, that's a bad idea.
你绝不想和那些色情电话女在现实中见面
You never want to meet those phone sex women in person.
是啊 我知道 我刚就这么说的
Yeah, I know, that's what I said.
是我就不会这么做
I wouldn't do it.
好的 不要
Good. Don't.
Joe Joe 你有没有发现你告诉我
Joe, Joe, you realize what you're telling me
不要去做某事 但我本来就不会做的
not to do, I'm already not doing!
我知道绝对不能和色情电话女见面
Okay, I know you should never meet a phone sex operator.
好吧? 我不是白痴
All right? I'm not an idiot.
我绝不会去见那种人的 绝不
I would never meet one of those people, ever.
好 不要
Good. Don't.
各位 我必须要看看她是否真人也是和
Guys, I have to see if she's as special in person
电话中一样很特别
as she is on the phone.
另外 如果我要是听你们的话
Besides, if I listened to you guys,
我就绝不会得到那个为婴儿替坐的工作了
I never would've got that job as a seat filler for fetuses.
好了 让我们来看看你的宝宝 好么
Okay, let's take a look at your baby, shall we?
嗨
Hi.
他一会就回来 去上厕所了
He'll be right back; he's in the bathroom.
谢谢你让我过来 Bonnie
Thanks for having me, Bonnie.
我只想找个人好好谈谈
I just needed someone to talk to.
没问题 Lois
Sure, Lois.
你现在在想什么
What's on your mind?
那个 说来话长
Well, it's kind of a long story.
你看...
You see...
八个**的小时之后
Eight (bleep) hours later...
罗伯特·劳吉亚 Robert Loggia 美演员 导演
天啊
Oh, my God!
那么 据Peter所知
So, as far as Peter knows,
他是准备搞外遇咯
he's about to cheat on you?
Lois 你必须要摊牌了
Lois, you got to draw the line here.
我知道
I know.
Peter有很多疯狂的事情我都会对他网开一面
There's a lot of crazy things I'll let Peter get away with.
他经历那段动漫时期时我都没说什么
I even held my tongue when he went through that anime phase.
嘿 Lois 我开车去超级快乐蚌酒吧
Hey, Lois, me make drive time to super fun Clam
和高贵Quagmire还有轮椅怪Joe一起
with noble Quagmire and wheel-monster Joe.
行动吧
Go, force!
[圆蛤汽车旅馆 8 P.M.]
Peter 你...
Peter, what...
你怎么穿成这样
Why are you dressed like that?
你对你的头发干了什么
What did you do to your hair?
出差 Lois 要去芝加哥城
Business trip, Lois. Going to Chicago City.
噢... 好吧
Oh... okay.
我知道了
I see.
而且 万一你们好奇想知道
And in case you're wondering why
我为何没有业务报表的话 其实我有
I don't have business charts, yes, I do.
好了 我要和孩子们道别了
All right, I got to say good-bye to the kids.
嘿 小子
Hey, champ.
我希望你能收下这怀表
I want you to have this pocket watch.
它还能走 就算它上面
It still works, even though it's got
沾满了内战时的脑浆也一样
a lot of Civil War brains all over it.
Meg 我希望你能收下这悲鸣似的屁
Meg, I want you to have this sad-sounding fart.
Chris 人们将会告诉你
Chris, people are gonna tell you
你是个笨蛋而且一无是处
that you're stupid and that you're no good.
再见 Otis
Bye, Otis!
这狗娘养的
That son of a bitch.
你好
Hello.
你...
You're...
你真美
you're beautiful.
既然你非要见我不可
So you got to meet me.
我们要做还是怎么着
Are we gonna do this or what?
听着 我...我得向你坦白
Listen, I... I got to be honest with you.
我其实不是
I am not, in fact,
风火轮车模公司的总裁
the President of Hot Wheels.
还有关于那个大厨帽我也撒谎了
And I also lied about the giant chef's hat.
我一顶也没有
I do not have one.
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
小谎并不重要
Well, the small lies don't matter.
我们开始吧
Let's go.
我为什么要这么做
Why am I doing this?
知道么 我有这世上最好的妻子
You know, I got the greatest wife in the world.
我们还有一个美丽的孩子
And we have one beautiful child.
但你是否感觉过有什么东西缺失了呢
But did you ever feel like something was missing?
知道么 就是你曾经拥有过
You know, something you had once,
但是现在却失去的
but now it's gone?
你是说对某个你信任的人的忠诚么
You mean like the loyalty of someone you trusted?
是的 我完全明白那种感觉
Yes, I know exactly what that feels like.
是啊 我是说 我第一次打给你
Yeah, I mean, I was just goofing around
只是想瞎聊聊 但当我听到你的声音
when I first called you, but when I heard your voice,
我-我感觉我找到了我失落的那部分
I-I felt like I found some part of me that was lost.
完全说不通 但是...
Doesn't make any sense, but it...
感觉某种神秘的力量想让我们相遇
it felt like some force in the universe wanted us together.
这话... 挺中听的
That's... kind of nice.
我想我能理解
I guess I could understand that.
既然你现在就在我面前
Now that you're here in front of me,
我想你是我见过最美的女人
I think you're the most beautiful woman I've ever seen.
八个**的(双关)小时之后
Eight (bleep) hours later...
啊 我必须要说 我太牛逼了
Ah, I got to say, I was fantastic.
你真这么想? 你这下贱的烂骗子
You think so, you dirty, rotten cheater?!
Lois!
你-你-你就是那个电话女郎
You-you-you-you is the phone lady,
你是那个电话 你是哪个电话
you the phone, you the phone,
你是那个电话女郎 你是那个电话女郎
you is the phone lady, you is the phone lady,
你是那个电话女郎...
you is the phone lady...
- 你欺骗了我 - Lois
- You cheated on me! - Lois!
你为什么会去做色情电话的工作
Why the hell were you doing phone sex?!
我是在养家糊口
I was providing for our family.
你在骗人
You were lying.
我开始觉得那整个芝加哥城
I'm starting to think that whole Chicago City
出差的故事真是一堆屁话
business trip was just a bunch of baloney!
这不是重点
That's not the point!
好吧 如果你想一想
Well, if you think about it,
我-我其实没有出轨因为是和你啊
I-I wasn't really cheating 'cause it was with you.
但你之前不知道是我啊
Well, you didn't know that!
是 但你知道么
Yeah, but you know what?
在某种意义上 我想我知道
In some way, I think I did.
其实 当我在电话上听到你的声音
You know, when I heard your voice on that phone,
我-我就有了种感觉
I-I felt something.
就像是本能 知道么
It was like an instinct, you know?
我的心和鸡鸡
Both my heart and my wiener
莫名的知道你就是我的灵魂伴侣
somehow knew you were my soul mate.
那个...
Well...
我想你一定爱煞我了
I suppose you did fall for me pretty hard.
你还不明白么 Lois
Don't you see, Lois?
我又爱上你了一遍
I fell in love with you all over again.
还有 听着 现在我们因为这事儿有了几年来最美妙的性爱
And, look, now we just had the best sex in years because of it.
我知道 就像我们的私处在沼泽中
I know. It's like our privates were shaking hands
成功商务会议后的握手一样
after a successful business meeting in a swamp.
对我来说 这... 这证明了
To me it... it just proves
我们是天生的一对
that we're truly meant to be together.
噢 我爱你 Peter
Oh, I love you, Peter.
我也爱你 Lois
I love you, too, Lois.
对了 你也许得成为一个全套都来的鸡了
By the way, you may have to become a full-on prostitute,
因为我们的电话账单是7000刀
'cause our phone bill was $7,000.
哦 Peter
Oh, Peter.
我想让你拼命的干我 这样我们就不得不换教堂了
I want you to do me so hard that we have to change churches.
恶心
Gross!
我太想蹂躏你了
I want to wreck you so bad,
你会被蹂躏成开垦过的热口袋牌卷饼一样
you'll look like an exploded Hot Pocket.
一种早餐品牌 类似卷饼 内有各种奶酪 蔬菜和肉等
天啊
Oh, my God!
你们有兴趣和我来个2又1/4P么
Can I interest you guys in a two-and-a-quarter way?